"Previously on The Mentalist..."
- You really like this guy, huh?
- He got a promotion in D.C.
- and he asked me to go with him.
- Yeah.
- Have you told Jane you're leaving yet?
- No. No, not yet.
I really want you
to be happy.
And that is the most important thing
to me...
That you do what makes you happy.
I wish we were
somewhere more romantic
but what the hell?
Will you marry me?
Um, wow. Marry you?
Um...
You're very chipper today.
Why not?
I thought you'd be sad
about Lisbon leaving for D.C.
Oh, Lisbon's not leaving.
She likes to talk like she might
but I don't think she's going anywhere.
From what I heard, it's a done deal.
She put in her transfer papers.
She starts work at the D.C.
office next month.
She's leaving Austin in a week,
next Friday.
Morning.
Captain Muller, campus police.
Cho. This is Jane.
This way, fellas.
We got a call at 6:07 a.m.
Housemates woke up and found him
like this.
Name's Tyler Vankamp...
Sophomore studying business.
- Practice-squad linebacker.
- You sure about Lisbon?
Did you hear it from her or did
you hear it from other people?
Say?
That's okay, sir.
He's talking to me.
I heard from other people...
Abbott.
Well, it's not a done deal, then, is it?
It's just a rumor.
Jane, she's leaving.
I'll believe it when I hear it from her.
- Just telling you what I heard.
- Uh, excuse me?
What?
- Tyler Vankamp.
- Yeah, we're on it.
Where are these, uh, housemates?
This way.
Hello. Finally.
We've been sitting here
like two hours, dude.
- You guys heard of human rights?
- No such thing.
Which one of you found Tyler's body?
- I did.
- What time was that?
6:00 a.m.
What were you doing up
at 6:00 a.m.?
Me and Colt go running.
You guys have any playing cards?
- No.
- Yes.
- Some... place.
Over there. First drawer.
Aha.
Yes.
She's leaving a week from Friday?
Yeah.
- That's only 10 days.
- Yeah.
When was the last time
anyone saw Tyler alive?
I-I came in at like 2:00,
and he was up studying.
Right there on the couch, totally chill.
We figured he must have surprised
a sneak thief.
- We need to go, Cho.
- We're working.
Uh, yeah. Sorry. This.
I almost forgot to say it.
It was all of them.
The ninja knife wasn't in
more than an inch
not deep enough to kill him,
so, uh, he was drowned.
- In a kiddie pool?
- Well, if someone was helping him along.
I mean, a big, athletic guy like Tyler
I would guess that that would be
a job for two people.
- Yeah, but why drown him?
- Well, probably something to do
with the drunken card game
that took place here last night.
They used toy money as chips.
Tyler was a player, huh?
Flashy gold watch, slick sneakers.
I bet he knew how to play cards.
I bet he won a lotta money.
Money that none of you could spare.
Then someone accused him
of cheating.
That would be you with the red eyes
and the turtleneck
to cover the bruises on your neck.
- What's your name?
- Barry.
Barry.
Tyler's an angry steroid freak.
He got mad.
He smashed a chair
and started throttling you
until, uh, this brave man
stepped in to help you
and received a punch
in the face for his trouble.
Hence the, uh, badly applied makeup
covering your black eye.
You applied the makeup.
You wear your watch on your right hand,
probably left-handed.
So judging by the angle
and the depth of the wound
I would guess that it was you
that stabbed Tyler in the back
to stop him from throttling Barry here.
Now, stabbing Tyler in the back
didn't help much.
It made him madder.
He chased you outside.
He fell in the pool.
That's when you two
with the still-damp sneakers
got on top of him and held him
down until he drowned.
Then you all came inside
and cleaned the room.
Now, what self-respecting student
voluntarily throws away
perfectly good vodka?
Can we go now?
I have stuff to do.
I guess so.
You're all under arrest.
- "Thank you."
- "You're so welcome."
- Oh, I'm gonna miss you so much.
- Me too. It was sweet.
What's with all the hugging?
You leaving today?
Tomorrow.
Are you still mad at me?
Do I look mad?
Yeah, you do.
Well, maybe I am.
Jane, this is something I need to do.
Please, just be happy for me.
I am happy for you.
I'm just a little sad for me
because you're leaving.
I'm not mad about it.
I just feel a little slighted
because I was the last to know.
You know damn well
why I couldn't tell you.
It's hard. We've worked together
a long time.
So stay. Don't go.
Don't break up the team.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I'm happy for you.
You know I'm happy for you.
You deserve this. You...
You deserve him.
He's a good man.
Thank you.
All right, people, gather up.
This letter was sent to Chief Agent Shultz
by U.S. mail, arriving an hour ago.
"Remember Greta De Jorio?
That was me."
"To honor Greta's memory"
"I will start killing again
very soon and very publicly."
"And you FBI simpletons
still won't catch me."
"Ask yourselves...
do you understand"
"752 598
H is M Key O?"
Interesting.
Greta De Jorio was murdered
five years ago
in Miami Beach, Florida
and the FBI team down there
worked the case hard
but nobody was ever charged.
She was a prominent socialite
so the Bureau got beat up a lot
in the press at the time.
De Jorio's body was found
in the trunk of her burnt-out car
on a remote dirt road
in the everglades.
Why was the letter
sent to Austin, not Miami?
We assume it's because the chief
was running the Miami office
of the Bureau at the time.
Perhaps this guy has a grudge
against her.
There's nothing in the letter to prove
it's from the actual killer.
That's true.
But if this unsub kills again
and brags about outwitting the Bureau
it could be a PR nightmare.
The chief is throwing everything
that we've got at this.
Leave and transfers are canceled.
Everybody that is here now
is working on this case
and no other until we get results.
Boss, no transfers? I-I'm supposed
to leave for D.C. tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Teresa.
No exceptions.
Cho, Fischer, get a team together,
head down to Miami.
Start by finding and debriefing
all of the original investigators.
Okay? Jane, any read on this code
or whatever it is?
Nope.
All right.
Wylie, start crunching that.
Jane, a moment in my office, please.
We'll close this one quickly.
He wants to be caught.
Besides, we get to go to Miami.
That's a fun place, right?
I guess.
So cheer up.
This is gonna be our last case together.
Let's make it a happy one.
It's a murder case.
Well... Yeah.
We've had fun before, haven't we?
You know what? You're right.
I'll cheer up.
Great.
- Good.
- Okay.
You're acting weird.
- Weird?
- Yeah.
You're acting cool about stuff
that I know you can't be cool with.
Anything you wanna tell me?
No.
All right.
Wow, huh?
- "Look at those sailboats."
- "Yep, it's beautiful."
Yeah. Yeah.
Pelicans, too.
Yeah, you won't see a view like this
behind a desk in D.C. though, huh?
This is the third time today
you've said something like this.
And you're correct. There are
no pelicans or sailboats in D.C.
but I'll manage somehow.
Yeah, I'm just saying.
"Yeah, yeah. No."
Uh, look, I don't care.
Just do it.
Hi. Don De Jorio.
FBI, huh?
Okay.
I got 10 minutes. Shoot.
There's been a development
in your wife's case.
Oh, this is Megan, by the way.
Hi.
- Wife number two?
- Number three, actually.
But who's counting?
And this is my lawyer, Ted Randolph.
- Good morning.
He's here because last time 'round
you federal geniuses
tried to pin this murder on me.
Now, is this more
pointless harassment
or did you actually catch somebody?
- No, sir.
- We received a letter from the killer.
It says he's gonna kill again.
W-what does that have to do
with Mr. De Jorio?
He was thoroughly investigated
and conclusively exonerated.
Not by me.
I'm kidding. That was a little joke.
Actually, I don't think
that you killed your wife.
- I have a different theory.
- Yeah? What's that?
Hey, there.
Come on in.
Oh. Chris. Christie, come here.
This is my daughter, Christie.
Chris, these people are here
about your mother.
Some wacko sent a letter.
Hi, Christie. Nice to meet you.
Now, what's this theory of yours?
I think this letter
wasn't written by the killer.
I think this letter was written
by someone
who thinks they know who the killer is
someone who wants revenge...
- Someone devilishly clever and patient.
- Really? Why?
Well, imagine if you're the killer
and you read this letter.
It would freak you out, wouldn't it?
Here's the FBI.
They're on your trail again.
Why? What's it all about, huh?
Why are they pretending to be you?
Why now?
What does this code mean?
It's possible, or it was sent
by the actual killer.
Don't waste your time.
The killer is Wes Baxter,
like I've always said.
Don, let's stick to the essentials here.
Wes Baxter. He did it.
Wes Baxter was a prime suspect
but he was cleared in the investigation.
They just couldn't nail him.
He lived next door.
The little creep was always
spying on Greta, stalking her.
- It was him!
- Christie.
What do you think of Wes Baxter?
- It doesn't matter what I think.
- It matters a lot.
Tell us.
He was okay. I liked him.
- Chris.
- She's speaking.
He didn't kill Mom.
You know, Chris has been through
a lot, all right?
Now, she doesn't remember
everything so clearly
- so why don't you just leave her out of it?
- No, Dad, I remember.
You hounded Wes like you know
he did it, but you don't know.
Christie, you don't have to get upset.
I'm upset because you're being a jerk.
Excuse me, young lady.
That is no way to talk to your father
in front of company.
- Oh, you be quiet, you.
- Excuse me?
No, Megan, I don't excuse you.
You're a witch, and I hate you.
That is beyond rude
and completely unacceptable!
I am talking to you!
Hello? Are you gonna let her
treat me like that?
- We're gonna get going.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
- You gonna let her treat me...
- All right, all right, all right.
Come, come.
I want her out of this house. You need
to buy her that condo so she leaves.
"She's 19."
- We need to talk to Wes Baxter.
- Okay.
Married life, huh? Whoa.
Yep.
I mean no disrespect to your marriage.
I'm not getting married.
Well, you're moving
to a new state with a man.
Basically, you're getting married,
in effect.
I mean, lucky you've had
all that time to get to know him...
Weeks and weeks.
- Months.
- A month, even.
I was thinking
about what you were saying
about the letter not being sent
from the killer.
If you're right, maybe it was
the daughter.
There was a five-year gap.
She would've been 14
at the time of the murder...
Too young to take action until now.
That's a great idea.
Yeah.
Could be her. Um...
What do you think this code means?
I don't know.
If you can't solve it, I definitely can't.
Well, I think if we put our heads together
we can solve it.
"752 598 H is M Key O."
It's not a phone number.
It's definitely not map coordinates.
What do you think?
- Well...
- 752 598.
A street address, maybe.
Too many numbers.
Yes.
Uh... or what about a date?
Like 752 would be July 1952.
Maybe. But why?
They're out back.
Exhale, Warrior II.
Beautiful.
Now flow through your vinyasa.
Excuse me. Monica Giraldi?
Yes.
Kimball Cho, FBI.
This is Agent Fischer.
You were Greta De Jorio's
business partner?
Well, a friend more than
partner, but... yes.
Why? What's happened?
Have you caught someone?
Oh, my God.
Everything okay, Monica?
Yes. Thank you, Tanya.
I'm sorry.
It's just brought that whole terrible
time flooding back.
Greta and I were friends at college.
We were... close, like close.
We, uh, both loved interior design
so going into business together
was a no-brainer.
Our firm started taking off
as she died.
I mean, I continue to run the firm
but it wasn't the same.
She was such a joyous person.
What was her state of mind
in the days leading up to her death?
Did she express any anxieties or fears?
I never told anyone this
but a few months before she died
she told me she was having an affair...
That it was real love,
and she'd never been happier.
Why didn't you tell
the investigators at the time?
I didn't wanna make her look bad.
- Did she give you a name?
- No.
I begged, of course, but she wouldn't.
She never mentioned him again
so I figured the affair
ended badly, you know?
They usually do.
Real...
Real what?
Jane, could you turn that down?
I'm sorry, Cho. I couldn't hear you.
What was that?
Okay. Got it.
See you later.
Greta was having an affair.
With who, we don't know.
An affair. Of course. Well,
that's relationships for you, isn't it?
They always seem to end up
in a tragic web
of deceit and betrayal, don't they?
The ones we see? Of course they do.
Stop it.
- Stop what?
- Trying to convince me not to leave.
Oh, come on. I know better than that.
Once you've made your mind up,
it's made up.
- For better or for worse...
- Shush.
- Richer or poorer.
- Seriously? Not funny.
Wesley Baxter.
- You, you think this is me?
- No.
- I-I swear to God...
- Relax. It's okay.
We, we can tell
that you've never seen this before.
Relax?
You people destroyed my life.
I mean, my own parents
thought I was guilty.
You were a legit suspect. The file
says that you were stalking Greta.
You were spying on her.
I-I didn't. I wasn't...
stalking Greta.
- Of course.
- What?
You were spying on Christie.
No. I...
I mean...
Kind of.
I was watching Christie.
I was in love with her.
I was just a stupid kid.
Why didn't you say anything
about this then?
Oh, sure. That would've made
everything all right.
I mean, she was 15.
I was 18.
You do the math.
Well, for what it's worth,
we talked to Christie
and she always thought
you were innocent.
She did?
- She said that?
- Yeah, she did.
Does that code mean anything to you?
- Nope.
- Okay, well, you keep that copy
and if anything, anything comes
to mind, you let us know, huh?
- Okay.
- Thanks for your time.
I think he's telling the truth.
I agree.
Let's go to the beach,
take a little walk.
It's close to here.
- We're working.
- Oh, come on. Live a little.
Well, this is nice.
We don't take enough time
to do stuff like this.
That's because we're wasting time.
Well, okay. Let's solve
that code, then, shall we?
Just like that, huh?
"Ask yourselves...
do you understand."
Well, that's an odd turn of phrase.
Must have some hidden meaning.
Ask yourselves...
do we understand?
Do we understand?
Do we? Do we understand?
- Dewey.
- Do we? That's what I said.
- The Dewey decimal system.
- Oh!
That's what the numbers stand for.
It's a way of cataloging library books.
Oh. 752 598.
752 is color
and 598 means bird.
Color bird, what does that mean?
There's no number for specific colors
so it's blue bird, red bird, whatever.
H, H, the radio call sign
for H is hotel.
There's a Blue Bird Lodge
on the Islamorada in the Keys.
"Is M Key."
Islamorada, Key.
Lisbon, you solved it.
- I did, didn't I?
- You did.
- But what does the O at the end mean?
- Oh. Uh... It's a date.
- O is a date?
- O, it's the astronomic symbol
for, uh, the full moon.
It's a full moon tomorrow night.
You just cracked the case.
- We cracked it.
- If you asked nicely
I would bet that Abbott will let you go
back to Washington right now.
Are you kidding me?
I wouldn't miss this for the world.
I'm gonna be on the Islamorada
tomorrow night.
- I did it. I did it.
- You did it.
I did it this time, not you.
- Who did it? It was me. I did it.
- You did it.
"Welcome to the Blue Bird."
You have adjoining waterside suites
just as you requested, Mr. Jane.
- Thank you.
- Sounds expensive.
Well, why not?
You know, it could be our last, uh...
Hurrah.
Someone may call the hotel
asking for a Greta De Jorio.
Anyone that does that,
give them my room number.
The room number, but not my name.
And, uh, tell the night staff
to do the same, yes?
- Certainly, sir.
- Thank you.
- Just your room number, De Jorio.
- Perfect.
Oh, would you like me to confirm
your dinner reservation?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Certainly.
Just so you know, um,
evening attire is preferred.
I'll, I'll just get a sandwich
or order room service.
- I don't have anything to wear.
- Oh, we'll figure it out. Thank you.
It's right up the stairs on the first floor.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
Beautiful.
Hey.
Jane, this is too much.
It's too nice. We're on a case.
Well, it might be our last case
together, so, uh...
How could anything be too nice?
The dresses are beautiful.
I'll see you at dinner.
Hello?
Huh? Yeah.
Here? Now?
Hey, Jane. Nice place.
Our unsub has good taste, huh?
Yeah. W-what are you guys
doing here?
Lisbon and I can handle this.
Well, this is a big case
with a whole lotta downside potential.
D.C. wants to put senior agents
on the scene.
Why? Do you have a problem
with that?
Nope. No problem.
I'm starving. How's the food here?
Yeah, apparently, it's good.
No burgers.
You know, I wish my wife were here.
Women really love this kinda stuff.
Yeah, they do.
Hi. I was wondering...
My boyfriend would love
the bathrobe in the room.
- Could I buy one?
- Oh, there's no need, ma'am.
The package Mr. Jane booked
last week
actually includes
a complimentary robe.
That's great.
Wait. Um...
Last week?
He booked the room last week?
Yes, ma'am.
- The wine list, sir.
- Oh, no, thank you.
Teresa.
Wow. You look spiffy.
Tell me something...
how is it possible
that you booked the rooms here
last week
two days before the letter
even arrived?
Okay, um...
You got me.
I wrote the letter. It was me.
It was, uh, just a ruse,
but, uh, I'm 100% confident
that it's gonna smoke out the killer.
You son of a bitch!
Maybe I should, um...
go and talk to her.
Yeah.
Uh...
Probably should order without us.
Yeah. Okay.
Hey, you know, I will take
a look at that wine list.
Thank you.
I need a taxi to the airport right now.
Okay. Thank you.
"Lisbon?"
Go away!
Please open the door.
Go away.
You know, I'm...
I'm sorry that I tricked you.
I just...
I just, uh...
You just what?
Jane, what were you doing?
I just don't want you to leave.
You don't give a damn
about what I want or need.
I am just a convenience for you.
You used me.
"It's all about you."
You used a-a woman's murder, Jane.
You basically dug her corpse up
for this crap.
You are so twisted up
in your own dishonesty
"you have no idea how to act
like a decent human being."
No idea.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
All right, well, if you're really sorry
why don't you just leave me alone?
"Go away!"
I know you're there.
I can hear you breathing.
Just leave me alone.
- Hey, it's me.
- Hey, sweetheart, how are you?
Good. Good. Um...
Listen, if the offer still stands,
the answer is yes.
Let's get married.
Yes!
Good. Good. Well, I'm...
I'm on my way to D.C. now.
Okay. All right, all right.
Text me your flight information
"and I'll be there."
"Teresa, it's gonna be great."
"You're gonna love the neighborhood."
"It's, it's full of restaurants,
your favorite kind."
"I got a number to an excellent broker"
"and, apparently, he's got some
appointments set up for us."
He stood in my office,
looked me in the eye
and lied to me, and I bought it.
Don't feel bad.
Jane could sell cats to mice.
I hope he's fixed things
with Lisbon, though.
Yeah.
- Think we should go check on him?
- No.
It's weird how mad she got.
I mean, he's pulled way worse stunts
than this.
He buried a man alive once.
She wasn't nearly as angry as this.
Really?
You don't know why?
Don't know why what?
Flight 407 to Washington, D.C.
will begin boarding in 45 minutes.
"We apologize for the delay."
"If there's anyone who has any hand
baggage they'd like to check"
"please come see me at the desk."
You're the FBI man, Jane.
Oh, you're the lawyer,
uh, Randolph, right?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I don't understand what's going on here.
You killed Greta De Jorio?
What? No, I didn't kill Greta.
Yeah.
Oh!
You're her secret lover.
How...
Yes.
I solved the clue in the letter
and I came here
to kill the bastard that killed Greta.
That's so romantic.
Uh, do-do you mind putting
the gun down, please?
Did...
Did you catch him already?
Yeah, no. I...
I-I wrote the letter, not the killer.
- What?
- Yeah...
It's a long, sad story, but don't worry.
The killer will show up.
Well, that's the plan, at least.
Can I get you a drink?
Yeah, sure.
Vodka, rum, gin, or whiskey?
Uh... Gin.
Hands up.
Oh. Wes Baxter.
- Hi. Welcome.
- You.
W-what the hell?
Who's this?
- Is this him? Is this the killer?
- No, no. He's not the killer.
And, uh, you're not the killer
either, are you?
- No.
- No. Didn't think so.
Uh, you mind putting the gun down?
Thank you.
You came to seek revenge, too, huh?
I shouldn't have made
the clue so easy.
Whoever killed Mrs. De Jorio...
he ruined my life.
Uh... vodka, rum, gin, or whiskey?
Rum.
Greta and I were deeply in love.
She was gonna divorce Don
and marry me.
I called it off.
I ended the affair.
I was afraid of the scandal and the damage
it would do to my business.
I was a coward.
Blind, stupid coward.
I was so filled with fear and self-hatred
that I destroyed the best thing
that ever happened to me.
By the time I realized my mistake...
it was too late, she was gone.
I'm sorry, man.
Bummer.
I have to go to the airport.
What's his deal?
You gotta be kidding me.
Turn around.
Hands up.
- Put your hands up.
- You must be Monica?
- I'm kind of in a hurry here.
- Who are you people?
And why did you send that letter?
Uh...
I know you.
You're the lawyer, Randolph.
Got old, huh?
And you. You're the kid
from next door.
So, who are you?
Okay, I-I-I don't want you
to be alarmed
but I'm, uh, FBI.
If you leave now
I will bet that you get away
before my colleagues get here
but you have to leave right now.
You're lying.
You're not a fed.
I-I know that I don't look like one
but I assure you I am one.
Show me your badge.
Okay. There we go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Damn.
He is. He's FBI.
I told you this was a setup. I told you.
Damn it, Monica!
Okay, just calm down.
If there were more FBI around
they'd be here by now, wouldn't they?
It's just him.
I don't see it.
They're like brother and sister.
There's no way.
Oh, speak of the devil,
a text from Jane.
"SOZ."
SOZ.
- S.O.S.
- Oh.
- So, what do we do?
- I'm thinking.
Listen, ladies, all you've done so far
is wave a gun around.
That's no big deal, huh?
- No one's calling you killers.
- I am.
No one can prove anything, can they?
You walk away now
and let your lawyers fix this.
He's right.
What else can we do?
We can just walk away?
Yeah, but you have to go right now
before my colleagues arrive.
Before anyone gets hurt...
go.
- Okay, let's go.
- Attagirl.
- Stay right where you are.
- Oh, dude.
Put your hands up.
Do it.
Now put the gun down.
Don't move!
Ow! My ears!
- That is loud!
- Oh, you're fine.
And, uh, yeah, you're fine.
It's just a flesh wound, okay?
I have to go, but help
will be here momentarily, okay?
Jane, what the hell?
You have a car with a siren, right?
I need your car keys.
- What?
- I need your car keys.
I gotta get to the airport.
It's an emergency.
- Where's Lisbon?
- She's at the airport.
- Oh, I see.
- Thank you.
Hey, hey, hey. You wanna
give us some guidance?
Yes. Uh, those two are the bad guys.
They're the good guys.
And blondie's an embezzler, I suspect.
- Hey, Cho.
- Hey.
- Thanks. Good luck.
- Where's he going?
"This is Lisbon.
Leave a message. I'll call you back."
Uh, Lisbon. It's...
it's Jane.
If you get this, call me, please.
Please?
Sorry. FBI, FBI.
Uh, you gotta let me through.
- ID?
- Yeah. Uh...
Oh.
Uh, it's in my car.
My car is out the front.
It's a federal vehicle out the front.
Next.
Wait! Wait!
Hang on!
Wait!
Hang on a second!
Hello! Hello! Let me in?
Let me in, please.
- Yes?
- Thank you. FBI. Won't be a moment.
- FBI? What's wrong?
- Uh, yeah, nothing.
Nothing to worry about.
Just a routine check.
- There you are.
- What are you doing here?
- There's something I need to say.
- I don't wanna see you. Go away.
You're right. You're right.
I-I have forgotten how to act
like a normal human being.
And I play games, I lie and I...
and I trick people
to avoid the truth of how I feel.
And the idea of letting anyone
close to me
is-is-is terrifying,
for obvious reasons.
But the truth, Teresa is that...
I can't imagine waking up
knowing that I won't see you.
The truth is...
I love you.
You can't imagine how good
that feels to say out loud
but it scares me...
and it is the truth.
It is the truth of what I feel.
It's too late.
Jane, it's too late.
Maybe. Maybe and I understand.
That's okay.
I needed to get to this,
and you deserve to hear it.
Put your hands in the air right now.
Do it!
I love you, Teresa.
And it makes me happy to be able
to say that to you.
I love her.
That woman in 12B...
You take care of her.
- I'm sorry. That was embarrassing.
- Oh, shush, honey.
Every woman on this plane
is green with envy.
The D.A. will press
for second degree and a plea
but I say we bid high
with murder one.
Okay. Why don't you take care
of processing?
I have to go to the airport
and try to persuade TSA to let Jane go.
He's still in custody?
They do not like people
messing with their airplanes.
Don't like it at all.
Hey.
Hi.
This is another fine pickle
you've gotten yourself in, huh?
Eh, I've seen worse, pickle-wise.
Yes, you have.
- How's the ankle?
- Oh, it's fine.
You didn't go to D.C.
No.
Did you mean what you said?
- Yes, I did.
- Good.
Just to be clear, we're talking
about pickles, right?
No. No.
The other thing.
Oh, that.
This is no joking matter.
Yes.
I meant what I said, every word of it.
Good.
Because I feel the same way.
Well, that's lucky.
What about Pike?
He'll understand.
- Say it again.
- Say what again?
Hey, quit that!